Oh man,
just a right there. Hey, how many
cleaners look? He said, "Nope." I hope
like hell he shipped that [__] charged.
Much is like 20,000 lb. It's It's heavy,
man. Well, we're getting an energy tank
delivered. Basically going to try and
convert trash to uh gasoline using
sunshine. They reuse boxes. It's a
wooden box with S clips. Oh, I love
that. You're going to use the box. A lot
of people say things about Wson, but his
character and his mission and the same
with ours. He wants to reuse, man.
That's Look, there's a solar panel, boy.
Look at that. Can't stop us. We're a
little [__] army of redneck. We just
need to get it anywhere off the road.
It's got a remote control and tank
tracks, man. We'll ride it in there.
Well, what have you done in the past?
Why don't we Hey, let's just roll it out
here. If you don't stop it on the end,
it's going to be on the ground. You got
to make sure to stop it. Remember when I
told you I said I need to be here to
receive this? This is what the hell I
was talking about. Well, I'm glad. Look,
I was Hey. I was like, I'm just going to
figure something out myself. Y'all need
to get down. You want us to? All right.
Hop off.
A [__] Redneck feet, right? This is how
you become a cult legend.
What's your name? TJ, man.
TJ, homie. I love the shirt. One, two,
three.
Y.
Yes, sir. This was not an average day at
work, was it?
It's a solar generator. I built one.
Yeah. In that van, I got 17.7 kwatt
hours. The same exact inverter, a 12vt
converter to step it down. Everything
runs off a 12vt with no inverter, so
it's completely efficient. A air
conditioner, a microwave, rolled it in
there, and ratchet strapped it down and
plugged the solar in. You're doing all
the fun stuff with solar. Hey, I'm a
true entrepreneur. Do you know what the
difference between an entrepreneur and a
business owner is? At one point, the
business owner realizes he is both the
lynch pin and bottleneck to his success.
A business owner usually has super high
work quality, is on the job every day,
has a couple very trusted employees, and
they do the good work all the time. But
the problem is if he is not there,
nothing goes right. An entrepreneur
builds businesses that run themselves.
You can install solar now. Imagine you
taking somebody who's never installed it
before and you have to tell them what to
do and you can't touch anything. Plug in
all the values from your electrical
plate, add a parallel string, click a
button, and have a PDF wiring diagram
emailed to you for free. So, man, you
want a hug? Come here, man.
I had to teach people in India's law so
they could like I translated this [__]
nine times things that you can select
need an inverter or have one. If you
select have one, it will tell you if
your system falls within the parameters
of your inverter specs. Say what's up to
the people on Instagram. Hey, got my
boys from New Orleans. Battery tank
right here. Joe Fails. Hey, we got it.
Nature Jab in the house. This is a
redneck reunion. There ain't a clean
foot in this [__] You know how
you shake a man's hand and if it's
rough, you tell he work. Now, if you
want to really know it, be like, "Man,
let me see your foot."
We're going to open this guy up.
What are we hitting on? We got to check
it out. This thing has a 100 kWh battery
bank, separate 50 amp outputs with
multiple charging ports, and a remote
control. Now you know why I [__] with
this man. It's a car.
That what I'm talking about. Roll around
in the hood in there. That's what I'm
talking about. Wait, is that really
100KW bank? Bro, that [__] sturdy. He's
already jealous. Look how cool we are.
Hey, bro. Wson don't even send
directions to me. He knows we ain't
reading [__] Here we go. Oh, here it
is. Holy [__]
That's 230 in. That's two separate 230
out, 230 in. That's each going to be 50
amp at about 12 1/2 KVA. Look at all of
your independent braking. Then you have
DC in. You can link these batteries
together in parallel, guys. Each one of
these is 90 to 230 volt up to 80 amp.
That looks like a giant cord. Is it
already plugged in? Oh, they made it
easy for us. It's a It's a courtesy.
That's a charge. Oh, yeah. For an
electric car, right?
There we go.
Status. Y 89%. Let's go. Who's played
the most video games here? Whoever's
done that, take this joystick. I'll take
it. Hey, Julie, you give me the P. You
get to drive this [__] up, dude. Even
the [__] latches are smarter than I
am. Neighbor. Yeah, I used to.
Dry that [__] over that box.
Let's do it. I guess there goes the
reusable box, right? Bro, somebody play
eye on the [__] tiger. Do you think
you could sell these? You think you can
sell these to a government? FEMA. Come
on, man. Man, that's what I'm saying. I
can sell water to a well. I can sell
leaves to a tree. I can sell a rock to a
dirt
you can pull up on the block anywhere.
Throw a block party. We do second lines
in New Orleans every Sunday, Monday. Um,
you can smoke blunts and drink beer on
this [__] I promise you this
[__] hood rich after working
hours.
Onward. Oh yeah. Look. Hey, just just go
ahead and ride. Somebody look, somebody
got to um hold this. Hey, this thing is
crazy.
I don't know what y'all are doing on
Friday, but we're riding on top of an
energy tank in the country and about to
go take trash and turn it into [__]
gasoline using sunshine. This is I
bought the solar panels. This is what
scientists really look like. You've been
tricked to think Damn right. You've been
tricked to think that they're people in
labs with like coats and [__] but they
really have all different creations
right here coming together to do
something for all of humanity. Yeah. On
an energy tank. Yep. We got Georgia,
Alabama. Uh notice the the dirty south
is leading the fight in climate change,
[__] Take heed in this [__]
Julian legit. I can see is just going
down the side of the highway with some
holes picking up trash.
Hey, we got a cooler hooked to the thing
in the back. I mean a fridge. We got a
[__] fridge with beer. Beer. Beer.
Oh, I have beer. You know I have beer.
It needs some Hennessy. Yeah. Yeah.
Goddamn Hennessy. You can't do a [__]
about Hennessy. I drink some Hennessy.
You had some Hennessy. I think I do.
Now, just to be smart, I think we should
hop off when we hit the mud hole and let
it let it I think it's going to hit the
mud just fine. Alex, look at the mud.
Powerful, man. It's powerful. All right.
Well, just cuz I don't want it. Even a
tank get stuck in the mud.
At least has that tow hook. You got All
right, we good. Let's go. Let's see.
Come on.
Oh, bro. Nothing.
Nothing. Hey, nothing. It's a tank.
It's a tank. What' you think was going
to happen, Joe? This is what happens
when you get a Chinese redneck and a
white redneck and a black redneck all
together in one place.